字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
最快首发美剧、日剧下载请登录
字幕组网站www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译:  冰蓝    euniceluo     洗七里
翻译:  MsFool    你想搭个雪太公吗
校对:  你想搭个雪太公吗
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第九集
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
手机APP搜索
人人影视字幕组
扫描二维码
关注凤凰八卦
-进来吧  -嘿
- Come on in. - Hey-o!
-嗨  -好啊
- Hi! - Hello.
喜欢我们的毛衣吗
Do you love our sweaters?
我觉得会超适合冰雪舞会跳舞
I thought they would be perfect for the Snow Ball dance.
我在那家有搭配商品的打折商店买的
I got them at the store where you buy things that go with the other things.
我知道那地方  我们就是在那买的
Oh, I know that place. That's where we got
"椒盐"造型的盐和胡椒粉调味瓶
our Salt-N-Pepa salt and pepper shakers.
椒盐是最成功的女子说唱团体之一
由三名黑人女性组成
克莱尔总是分不清哪个是哪个
Claire can never tell which one is which.
创意与呈现都很失败的产品
A confusing idea poorly executed.
别再暗示我是种族主义者了
Stop implying I'm a racist.
我们怎么就要去当监护人了
How did we get roped into this chaperone thing?
有个特别烦人的家庭教师协会的妈妈玛乔丽
This incredibly annoying PTA mom, Marjorie,
整天缠着我们为各种活动当志愿者
keeps hounding us to volunteer for things,
我们推脱到终于没借口用了
and we finally ran out of excuses.
我也许该告诉她我们出发了
Ooh, I should probably tell her we're coming.
信了她的邪
Unreal.
"你在哪里"
"Where are you?"
"你跟克莱尔在一起吗"
"Are you with Claire?"
"你还有多远"
"How far away are you?"
"快到了发短信告诉我"
"Text me when you're close."
"我把钥匙锁在车里了"
"I locked my keys in my car."
那是海莉发的
Oh, that's from Haley.
虽然我很想见见这个怪人
Much as I'd love to meet this dingbat,
但他们到底需要多少监护人啊
how many chaperones do they really need?
只用一个人就能拿着水管
Takes one person to turn a garden hose
浇醒发情的人们
on those dry humpers.
如果菲尔要去  那你也得去
If Phil is going, you are going.
我不喜欢在任何场合当唯一一个
I don't like being the only person in the room
没老公的人
without a husband.
这事让我没有安全感
It's my one insecurity.
菲尔在当老好人
Phil's just trying to be nice.
其实他也不想去
He doesn't want to go to this thing, either.
实际上我很期待
Actually, I was looking forward to it.
也许见见所谓的拉拉队员
Maybe meet some of these so-called cheerleaders.
我会告诉她们  我们可以将蝎子摆尾姿势的人
Watch their faces when I tell them we could kewpie a scorpion
往上扔  接住  然后搭架子
into a cradle catch
同时观察她们惊讶的表情
and then pop up into a split extension.
当然这些现在大多数都是禁招了
Most of that stuff's illegal now.
我觉得菲尔的意思是
I think what Phil's trying to say is that
我跟他很久都没有度过男人之夜了
he and I haven't had a boy's night in a good while.
就你跟我两个人出去玩玩
I mean, wouldn't it be nice to just hang out together,
难道不好吗
just you and me?
你怎么说  伙计
What do you say, buddy?
啥
What?!
跟我老丈人杰出去玩玩也许挺好的
Might be nice to have a hang with my boy Jay.
如果你没意见
If it's fine with you.
行啊  这是我至少能做的  因为明天
Sure, it's the least I could do, because tomorrow
你就要辅导卢克做家庭作业了
you are going to help Luke with his homework
而我要去葡萄酒庄
while I visit wine country.
我也想去
I want to go.
她的意思是躺在蹦床上
That's just what she calls lying on the trampoline
喝夏顿埃酒
drinking Chardonnay.
好  我们在路上了
Oh, yes! We're on our way.
-好  -再见
- Okay. - Bye-bye.
你俩玩得开心哦
Have fun, you two.
别操心我们  我们会嗨翻天的
Don't worry about us. We'll have a blast.
我们会过得很开心的
We'll have a good time. We'll have a good time.
好棒
Yes!
这会很好玩的
This is gonna be so great!
当然  等她们出门后
Sure it will. Maybe give them about
五分钟你再走吧
a five-minute lag time before you hit the road.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你说我们要一起去玩
You -- you said we were gonna do something together.
我是想帮我们摆脱愚蠢的舞会
I was just trying to get us out of that stupid dance.
好吧
Okay.
享受你的夜晚吧  菲尔
Enjoy your night, Phil.
我跟一本写坏警长的精彩西部小说还有约
I've got a date with an epic Western about a crooked sheriff,
而我读到了我预测是不当绞刑的桥段了
and I'm at the first of what I predict to be many wrongful hangings.
如果你不打算出去玩
Well, if you're not up for doing anything,
我还是去舞会好了
I think I'll just go to the dance.
什么  不  你不能那样做
What? No. You can't do that.
会显得我像是个混蛋
Makes me look like a jerk.
那我该做什么
Well, then what am I supposed to do?
-你想做什么都行  -我想去舞会
- Whatever you like. - I want to go to the dance.
你怎么就不懂我意思了呢
How are you not getting this?
好吧  我就回家好了
Fine. I'll just go home.
你要去舞会  对吧
You're going to the dance, aren't you?
-当然  -好  你赢了
- Of course I am. - All right, you win.
-我们一起玩  -太棒了
- We'll do something. - Awesome!
-你想做什么  -天啊  我不知道
- What do you want to do? - Gosh, I don't know.
我的舞蹈细胞还有些蠢蠢欲动
I mean, dancing is still so much in the air.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
苏格兰威士忌酒庄
Scotch country.
12号桶里冰块不多了
We're low on ice in bucket 12.
蟹肉饼得撑一晚上
Hey, those crab cakes have to last all night.
多推销奶酪
Push the cheese.
演出曲目
Setlist?
你要以《幸运儿[上床]》开场吗
You're starting with "Get Lucky"?
拜托  音乐有个故事起承转合好吗
Come on, we're telling a story here.
你知道现在几点了吗
Do you know what time it is?
我还以为你要帮我布置
I thought you were gonna help me set up.
抱歉
Sorry, buddy.
我在操心大局[大照片]
I was worrying about the big-picture stuff.
欢迎来到冰雪舞会
有足够的地方放吗
Hmm. Is there enough room for it here,
还是我该把它放在后门入口
or should I put it in the back entrance?
你绝对可以把它塞进某个"后入口"
You can certainly put it in a back entrance.
天啊  一切看起来都好棒啊
Oh, my gosh, doesn't everything look so lovely?
这是高中嘛
Well, it's high school.
随你怎么装饰  这里还是
Dress it up all you want, it's still the place I spent
我被虐待狂恶霸折磨了四年的地方
four years being tormented by sadistic bullies.
衬衫不错  米歇尔小妞
Nice shirt, Michelle.
知道吗  时代变了
You know what? Times have changed.
在高中  你想过
In high school, did you ever imagine
你会跟橄榄球教练在一起吗
you'd end up with the football coach?
橄榄球教练倒是没有
The football coach? No.
游泳教练阿提诺老师  我倒是每晚都想
The swim coach, Mr. Artino, almost nightly.
塔克教练  米奇尔
Oh, Coach Tucker, Mitchell.
谢谢你们当志愿者
Thank you for volunteering.
我拒绝不了嘛
I couldn't say no.
我队里的孩子几乎是恳求我来
The kids on the team practically begged me.
我这么重要  激励了这么多人  真是太好了
It's an amazing thing to matter so much and inspire so many.
不  我觉得他们希望你来
Oh, no, I think they just wanted you here
只是为了要整你
so they can prank you.
-是吗  -对
- Hmm? - Yeah.
橄榄球队计划好了一切
The football team has something all worked out.
我不知道详细招数  因为薪水有了上限后
I don't know what it is 'cause I checked out
我就走人了
after they capped my salary.
但向来是惨不忍睹  不忍直视
But there's usually a mess,
所以你最好在这精致的礼服外面套一个披风
so you might want to throw a poncho over all that finery.
我的天  我好讨厌恶作剧
Oh, my God, I hate pranks so much.
我整场舞会都只能提心吊胆
Now I'm gonna spend the whole dance paranoid
猜测他们要怎么整我
wondering what they're gonna do.
会不会很疼  我会不会哭
Is it gonna hurt? Am I gonna cry?
你是个小丑
You're a clown.
小丑不就是一直在耍别人吗
Isn't that mostly just pranking people?
不  才不是  小丑又有爱又欢乐
No, it is not. Clowns are loving and joyful.
你知道吗
You know what?
我对你们这种愚昧的想法早有耳闻
I was warned about this kind of ignorance.
不要让我后悔没跟马戏团圈内人结婚
Don't make me regret marrying outside the big top.
什么
What?
我们得擦亮眼睛看好
We got to keep our eyes peeled
那些尝试偷带酒进来的孩子
for kids trying to bring alcohol in here.
这工作不喝酒我没法干好
I cannot make it through this thing without a drink.
玛乔丽  十二点方向
Marjorie, 12:00.
天哪
Oh, God.
快  假装我们在吵架
Quick, pretend we're having a fight.
她就不会过来了
Then she won't come over here.
你偷了该我继承的遗产  你傍大款
You stole my inheritance, you gold digger!
你这话准备好很久了吧
Wow, you had that one ready to go.
你们在这啊
There you are.
你们收到我的短信了吗
Did you get my texts?
看看我没收的酒
Look what I've already confiscated.
真可耻  交给我吧
Oh, shameful. I'll take that.
我还需要志愿者打电话给家长
So, I still need volunteers to call parents
请他们提供无声拍卖会的拍品
for silent auction items.
我已经排了六个小时的班
I've divided it into six-hour shifts,
所以如果你们能轮流打半个小时电话
so if you switch ears every half-hour,
那就太棒了
it's actually not bad.
我能拜托你们两位女士吗
Can I count on you two ladies?
我太忙了  但我不能替歌洛莉亚做决定
I'm so busy, but I can't speak for Gloria.
偶电话英语不咋地
My phone English no so good.
我懂  我有点爱唠唠叨叨
I get it. I'm a bit of a nag-eroo.
就像我妈总开玩笑说
Like my mom always jokes,
你知道你该去烦谁吗
you know who you should bore with this?
你老公  对了  他离开你了
Your husband. Oh, right, he left you.
那个女人太神经兮兮了
That woman is so uptight.
你知道她需要什么吗
You know what she needs?
一个男人
A man.
你的想法太过时了
That is a very old-fashioned attitude,
但在这种情况下  还是很贴切的
which in this case, seems pretty accurate.
男人  男人  男人  我们去哪找个男人
A man, a man, a man. Where can we find one.
你好  Siri  录一下鉴宝节目
Hey, Siri, record "Antiques Roadshow."
我一个都想不到
I can't think of anyone.
布朗校长
Principal Brown.
他单身  我们可以撮合他们
He's single. We could fix them up.
在这个冬季舞会上相恋
At the winter dance. Mm-hmm.
太浪漫了
That's so romantic.
对  如果她能多关注自己
Yes, and maybe she'll get off our backs
就能少烦一点我们了
if she spends more time on hers.
你真是你爸的亲儿子
You really are your father's son.
你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
有人刚在所有人面前嘲笑了我的领结
Guy just made fun of my bow tie in front of everyone.
问我是不是故意gay里gay气的
Asked if I was trying to look gay.
不  你带着很好看
Oh, that is charming.
我猜高中还是以前的老样子吧
So I-I guess high school hasn't changed that much, has it?
听着  我想让你重新戴上这个领结
Look, I want you to put this back on
骄傲地戴着
and wear this with pride.
你扔进去之前它就湿透了  是吗
This was soaking wet before you threw it in there, right?
我们还是扔了它吧  没事的
We're gonna let it go. It's fine.
好了
All right.
吐槽你的蠢货在哪里
Where is this idiot?
你是故意想要gay里gay气吗
Are you trying to look gay?
因为你没有胸肌  没有大毛孔
'Cause you don't have the pecs, the pores,
也没有男子气概  猛男
or the pants for it, slugger.
有句比较老的话  跟你发型差不多年头
Hey, here's a reference that hairstyle's old enough to get.
发型不可则止  "舞"自辱焉
It's not twerking.
好吧  你就是个  就是个  是个...
Yeah, well, you're just -- you're just a -- you're a --
你是个  你是个...
You're a -- you're a --
我先去跳个舞啊
So, I'm gonna go squeeze in a dance real quick
你就慢慢在这里结巴说完这句话吧
while you stagger to the end of that sentence.
我是《每日海豚报》莱斯丽·关·柯林斯
Leslie Kwan Collins, Daily Dolphin.
我认识你好吗
I know who you are.
我们打从幼儿园就是朋友了
We've been friends since kindergarten.
你愿意评价一下我线人所说的
Care to comment on what my sources are calling
"有史以来最棒的冰雪舞会吗"
"The best Snow Ball ever?"
好  但这场派对的成功
Sure, but I'm not the one responsible
不是我一个人的功劳
for this party's success.
也是他们的
They all are.
我只不过是让这一切发生的谦虚公仆
I'm just a humble servant who made it all happen.
让我们单独谈谈好吗  谢谢
Can you excuse us, please? Thank you.
我真是服了你了
You are unbelievable.
打住  我承受不起那么多赞美
Stop. I can't keep hearing this.
我才是让这一切发生的人
I'm the one who made all this happen.
你知道凭八千块办起这活动有多难吗
Do you have any idea how hard it is doing all this for $8,000?
你当然不知道  因为...
Yeah, of course not, because --
等一下  舞会的预算是八百块块
Wait, wait, wait. The budget for this was $800.
你花了八千吗
You spent $8,000?
那可是一整年的经费预算
That's the budget for the whole year.
我发短信问你"冰雪舞会的预算是多少"
I texted you, "What's my budget for the Snow Ball."
你回复了八千  还有一张无聊的动图
You replied $8,000, followed by a gratuitous gif
一张男人撞到蛋蛋的动图
of a guy getting hit in the nards.
就像是在说  别在栏杆上滑板就好啦
It's like just don't skateboard down a railing, right?
-布朗校长  -什么事
- Principal Brown. - Yep?
如果我们学生会的预算想稍微超额
If we were to go over with the student council budget,
再多要一点预算会有多难呢
how hard would it be to get a little extra money?
没问题啊
Oh, no problem.
我们只需要把教员休息室里名画卖了就行
We would just sell the Rembrandt in the faculty lounge.
看到没  问题解决了
See? Problem solved.
-他是在说反话  -怎么了  有什么问题吗
- He's being sarcastic. - Why? What's wrong?
没有  只是在玩"如果钱都花完了"的游戏
Nothing. Just playing "What if all the money got spent?"
你能想象那情景吗
Oh, can you imagine?
预算没了我们就得取消
We'd have to cancel
其他所有的学校活动
every other school event,
先拿摔跤队的庆功宴开刀
starting with the wrestling banquet,
那些狂躁的神经病会把你们头拧掉的
and those hopped-up psychos would rip your heads off!
然后你们就会流血而死
And then you'd bleed to death
因为我们再也没钱请校医了  对吗
'cause we can't afford a school nurse anymore, right?
生蚝
Oysters.
想得美  小伙子们
Oh! Nice try, boys!
没你们的事了
You guys are cool.
快走开
Just, uh, move along.
小卡  你知道一个叫达米安·沃马克的小孩吗
Hey, Cam. Uh, do you know a kid named Damien Warmack?
当然知道
Oh, yeah.
-很刻薄的小孩  -对
- Mean little kid. - Yeah.
他嘲笑我所有的防守队员肥死人
He fat shamed my whole defensive line.
看着一个曾经彪悍的中卫把沙拉里的
There's nothing more sad than watching
烤面包丁挑出来  真是人间惨剧
a once terrifying nose tackle pick croutons out of his salad.
天啊  我现在好纠结
Oh, God, I'm so conflicted.
有个同性恋小孩在欺负橄榄球员
A gay kid is now bullying football players,
虽然看似是种进步
which I guess, you know, seems like progress,
但这种进步是错误的
but the wrong kind of progress.
您要不要吃点...
Would you like a --
反正大部分烤面包片最后都是被丢掉的嘛
In my defense, bruschetta mostly ends up on the floor anyway.
小卡  你好像
Cam, I think you might be
太过担心恶作剧的事了
more worried about this prank than you need to be.
真搞不懂他们为什么想要整我
Well, I just don't understand why they want to prank me.
我还以为他们喜欢人家
I thought they liked me.
他们当然喜欢你啦
Of course they like you.
对不喜欢的人那不叫整
You can't prank someone you don't like.
叫做...  叫做攻击
That's -- that's just assault.
但整你  其实是他们在用
But pranking you is their bizarre way
扭曲变态的方式向你表白
of saying that they love you.
这是你在用扭曲变态的方式安慰我吗
Is this your bizarre way of not validating my feelings?
我们可以去打保龄球
Okay, we could go bowling.
昨晚刚去打完  现在打球的兴致是"龄"
Hmm. Had my league last night. I'm a little bowled out.
好吧  那打一轮迷你高尔夫球呢
Fair enough. Round of mini golf?
好主意  你等着
Great idea. Wait up.
我去拿我的青蛙和弹弓
I'll go get my frog and my slingshot.
我们骑单车到下面去
We'll hop on our bikes and go down there.
要不我们吃点东西
We could get something to eat.
-吃过了  -看电影呢
- Already ate. - Go to the movies?
-讨厌排队  -去酒吧呢
- Hate the lines. - How about a bar?
我们大老远开车去
So, we drive across town, pay a 200% markup
花两倍的钱买跟我手上这杯一模一样的威士忌
on the same glass of scotch I'm holding in my hand right now
就为了有某个喝醉的老女人粘过来
just so some drunken old broad can stagger over
说我长得像某老派大牌男演员吗
and tell me I look like Ernest Borgnine.
我不要再提议了
You know what? I'm done trying.
和我做任何事都不能让你开心
I'm sorry there isn't a single thing
真是不好意思
you'd have fun doing with me.
得了吧
Oh, come on!
别一副受伤脸
Don't get all hurt.
我保证  我会答应你下一个提议
I promise your next idea, I'll say yes to.
不是吧
Really?
谢谢你  杰
Thanks, Jay.
坚持不懈地争取美好的事物
You held out for something awesome,
终有一天有了回报
and I think we nailed it.
请给我一杯
One, please.
饮品8块钱  小费随你给多少
That'll be $8, plus whatever tip you feel is appropriate.
一小时前明明还是免费的
It was free an hour ago.
以前把婴儿丢在车后座
You used to be able to throw a baby
不用婴儿座椅也没问题啊
in the back seat without strapping it in.
时过境迁  朋友
Times change, my friend.
迪尔加多
Hey, Delgado.
希望这宾治酒
I hope this punch isn't as watered down
里面掺的水份
as your performance in
不会像你在《欲望号上吊车》表演时一样多
"A Streetcar Named Desire to Hang Myself."
应为《欲望号街车》  著名电影
达米安  你真...  你看着很...  我靠
Damien, you're just -- you look -- damn it,
好欣赏你这外套  我好气啊
I hate how much I like that jacket.
我看穿你了
I know what you're doing.
什么
Excuse me?
我知道身为一个同性恋青少年很艰难
I know how hard it is to be a gay teen.
高中时  我只有一个朋友
In -- in high school, I only had one friend.
真的吗
Really?
奥斯卡·王尔德是怎么样的呢
What was Oscar Wilde like?
英国19世纪同性恋作家  诗人
你这是在使性子
You're lashing out.
因为你很愤怒  缺乏安全感
Because you're angry and you're insecure,
想要让大家跟你一样难受
and you just want everyone else to feel as bad as you do.
可能吧
Maybe.
不过你怎么会懂
But come on.
你长得像迈克尔·法斯宾德  肯定轻松得多
It must've been easier for you looking like Michael Fassbender.
德国男星  以性感著名
我才不像...
I do not look like --
你真的觉得我像迈克尔·法斯宾德吗
you think I look like Michael Fassbender?
当然  如果他再老一点  矮一点
Yeah, if he were older and shorter
并且由凯西·格里芬来扮演的话
and played by Kathy Griffin.
美国喜剧女星  也有一头红发
那个叫达米安·沃马克的小屁孩嘴真毒
Hey, hey. That Damien Warmack kid is so mean.
揪着其他可怜孩子的不安全感
Honing in on these poor kids' insecurities
狠狠地践踏他们的尊严
and then just lacerating them.
我长得才不像凯西·格里芬  对吧
I-I don't look like Kathy Griffin, do I?
我告诉你什么才叫恶毒
I'll tell you what's mean,
我的学生让我整晚干等着那个恶作剧
is my team making me wait all night for this damn prank.
或者"米奇  你想太多了
Or, "Mitch, you're being ridiculous.
你很帅  如果要由女人来扮演你
You're a very handsome man, and if you had to be played
也该是年轻貌美的安·玛格丽特"
by a woman, it would be a young Ann-Margret."
六七十年代美国女演员  也是红发
-教练  -天啊  动手吧
-Hey, Coach. -Oh, God! Just do it!
直接来吧
Just do it!
原来是布朗校长  对不起  我以为...
Oh, Principal Brown, sorry. Sorry, I thought --
我以为你就是那个恶作剧
I thought you were the prank.
恶作剧  不是的
Prank? Oh, no.
之前是我误会了
That was a little misunderstanding on my part.
原来他们整蛊的是新来的摔跤教练
Turns out the new wrestling coach is being pranked.
他们的招数是
Yeah, they're gonna do that thing where
把他转几圈
you spin a guy around a bunch of times,
让他晕乎乎的  然后把他绑在树上
you get him good and dizzy, and then you tie him
让他待一个周末
to a tree for the weekend.
天啊  你不是应该阻止他们吗
Oh, God. Shouldn't you stop them?
本来会的  但他最近老占用我的停车位
I would, but he's been parking in my spot lately.
他们不会来作弄我了  真是松了一口气
I guess it's a relief they're not pranking me.
没错  你终于可以放轻松了
Yes. You can finally relax.
真的可以吗
Can I?
威尔森教练才来了七个月
Knowing Coach Wilson's only been here seven months?
从来没给队员带过自制香蕉面包
He's never brought his team homemade banana loaf,
可他们已经在乎他到要吓唬他了
and yet they care enough to terrorize him?
行了  你到底是想被整还是不想被整
Okay, you're gonna have to land on a position.
我只是不明白他们为什么还求我来
I just don't understand why they begged me to be here
又不是为了整我
if they're not gonna prank me.
因为他们爱戴你
Because they love you,
你为他们的生命带来了改变
and you're making a real difference in their lives.
我  我
Oh, well, I-I --
我说笑而已  他们觉得你是个软柿子
I'm just kidding. They think you're a pushover,
你在的话  他们想干什么都行
and with you here, they can get away with anything.
真是笑话  没什么能逃过我法眼
That's ridiculous, because nothing gets past me.
给我  谢谢
Excuse me. Thank you.
-什么玩意儿  -看好了
- What is that? - Look at this.
我去把这个倒进"下水道"
I'm gonna go pour this down the drain.
干杯
Cheers.
玩得很开心吗
Having fun?
我只是尽力在撑门面
Hey, I'm just trying to keep up appearances.
如果我慌了  大家就跟着慌了
If I panic, everybody panics.
你在饮料台那里挣了多少钱
How much money did you make at the drink station?
只有200块左右
Only about $200.
足够了
That's enough.
我工作的乡村俱乐部  有个同事
A caddy at the country club where I work
在欣斯代尔的赛狗场有门路
knows this dog track in Hindsdale.
有只名叫"超灵小灵犬"的格雷伊猎犬
There's 40-to-1 odds on a greyhound,
赔率是40比1  它...
Whippet Good, who --
好吧  钱都输光了
Okay, the money's gone.
就一次
One time.
不要  太蠢了
No, it's stupid.
-就试一下  -我不会就范的
- Just try it. - I'm not doing it.
-周围又没人  -我懒得鸟你
- No one else is around. - I don't care.
别这样  我来起头
Come on, I'll start.
《狮王今夜沉睡》- Solomon Linda
* 在丛林里  这广袤的丛林里 *
* In the jungle, the mighty jungle -- *
好了  够了
All right, that's it!
给我出去  我们做点别的
Get out. We're doing something else.
有人看上你啦
Somebody thinks you're cute.
克莱尔  拜托  我们又不是在高中
Claire, please, this isn't high school.
好吧  等等  还真是在高中
Well, no, wait a minute. It is high school.
好吧  是谁
Mm. Okay. All right, so who is it?
我的最爱是1929年产的烤面包大师
My favorite is a 1929 Bread Master.
或许有些人会说
Some people might say
"多事"的人才把收藏古董"多士炉"当爱好
that collecting vintage toasters is a crumby hobby.
多谢捧场
Thank you.
玛乔丽  我刚刚在和布朗校长聊天
Marjorie, I was just talking to Principal Brown,
他对你有兴趣啊  老妹[黑人腔]
and he into you, girl.
真的吗  他可比三十年代的
Really? He's hotter than a 1930s
阳光牌烤面包机还火热
Sunbeam Toastrite.
千万别问啥意思
Don't.
我现在不方便聊天  老妈
I can't talk right now, Mom.
不是的  我才没周六夜独守空房
No, I'm not home alone on a Saturday night.
我在参加舞会  还有男生喜欢我呢
I'm at a dance, and a boy likes me.
咱们可行啦[黑人腔]
We good at this!
你为什么要这么说话
Why are you talking like that?
我也不知道
I don't know.
打扰一下  二位
Excuse me, hi. Hey.
我也不知道具体该怎么办
I don't know exactly how to do this,
能被美人垂青实在是荣幸之至
but I'm very flattered by your interest in me,
如您所料  我对您也有好感
and just so you know, the feeling is mutual.
什么
What?
我不知道你喜不喜欢露营
I don't know if you're into camping,
但我能搞来帐篷
but I can get a tent.
我已经结婚了  屁股的那一半在家呢
I'm married. My rear end is at home.
我说的是玛乔丽
I meant Marjorie.
不  她太神经兮兮了
Oh, no. She's way too intense.
谢了  再说一旦你想象过自己
No. And once you've imagined yourself
坐在篝火旁为歌洛莉亚吹单簧管
sitting by a campfire playing your clarinet for Gloria --
玛乔丽特别喜欢户外
Marjorie loves the outdoors.
是的  她还有个露营烤面包机
Yes, she even has a camping toaster.
她是位超级棒的女士
She is a super lady,
但二位  我才45岁
but, guys, I'm only 45.
我还期待营火后烟火般的美人呢
I'm holding out for fireworks.
达米安过来了
Oh, here comes Damien.
千万别告诉他我自以为能勾搭上歌洛莉亚
Do not tell him that I thought I had a shot with Gloria.
我妈不信布朗校长喜欢我
My mom doesn't believe that Principal Brown likes me.
你能跟她说说吗
Can you tell her?
歌洛莉亚
Gloria?
偶电话英语不咋地
My phone English no so good.
-去吃冰淇淋怎么样  -太凉了
- How about ice cream? - Too cold.
-喝咖啡呢  -太晚了
- Coffee? - Too late.
等一下  我真笨
Oh, wait a minute. I'm such an idiot.
我竟然忘了有知名牛仔演员的回顾影展
I forgot about the Clint Eastwood retrospective
展完还有苏格兰威士忌品酒会
followed by the scotch tasting
七十年代的著名运动员们会在那里
where famous athletes from the '70s tell stories
讲述过去扬斯敦的生活是怎样的
about how life used to be in Youngstown.
-真的吗  -假的
- Really? - No!
哪有这种活动
It doesn't exist.
你想参与的那种活动根本不存在
What you want does not exist.
你这是做什么
What are you doing?
我不管你要干嘛
I don't care what you do,
但我要去参加舞会
but I'm going into that dance.
我喜欢看到孩子们盛装打扮开开心心的
I like to see the kids all dressed up and happy
试图装出一副已经长大的样子
and trying to look older than they are.
我的初吻就是在高中舞会
The first girl I ever kissed was at a high school dance.
其实当时就放着《狮王今夜沉睡》
It was actually to "The Lion Sleeps Tonight."
难怪我刚刚脑子里一直回放这首歌
I guess that's why it was in my head.
姑且告诉你  狮王那晚可一夜都没睡
Let's just say the lion did not sleep that night.
我当时像个野蛮人一样狂灌汽水
I was slamming Mountain Dews like a wild man.
玛莎·古尔丁
Marsha Goulding.
我当时特别迷恋她
I had this huge crush on her.
终于鼓起勇气邀请她去春季嘉年华
Finally got my nerve up to ask her to the Spring Fling.
第一支舞时我吓坏了  总踩她脚
First dance, I was terrified. I'm tromping all over her feet.
但跳着跳着  就放松了
But as the dances went on, it got easier,
山姆·库克的《你令我沉醉》放到一半时
and right in the middle of Sam Cooke singing "You Send Me,"
我鼓起勇气一搏
I went for it.
我当时好惊讶她也回吻了我
I was just so surprised she kissed me back.
初吻不能再来
Well, you can't have your first kiss again,
但你的下一个吻就在那场舞会上
but you can have your next one right in there.
好啦好啦  就哄歌洛莉亚高兴高兴吧
Oh, what the hell. Give Gloria a thrill.
太好了  杰  因为你使她完整
That's great, Jay, 'cause you complete her.
菲尔你真会说话
Oh, Phil.
不  字面意义上的
No, literally.
"你使她完整"
You complete her.
你是这个笑话的结尾屁股部分
You're the butt of this joke.
毛衣给我
Give me the sweater.
玛乔丽又聪明又有条理
Marjorie is smart and organized,
不论你什么时候需要洗手液或是创可贴
and if you ever need hand sanitizer or a Band-Aid,
她总随身带着
she always has it on her.
她就像一个性感火辣的药房
She's like a sexy, sexy drugstore.
她萌得没治了
She's as cute as a button.
就像个长大的椰菜娃娃
Like a grown-up Cabbage Patch doll.
感觉麻烦事会特别多
Yeah. Yeah, that seems like it'd be a whole lot of e-mails.
坚决拒绝
It's a hard pass.
可是布朗校长  你知道人们都说
But, Principal Brown, you know what they say
在外面就充满热情的人妻回家后多狂野吧
about a mom who's enthusiastic in the streets.
哪有这种说法
That's not a saying.
话说回来  你们两个
Why are the two of you
为什么突然对我的感情生活这么感兴趣
suddenly so interested in my love life, anyway?
因为我们在乎你
Because we care.
你们连我的名字都不知道
You don't even know my first name.
我们知道
Yes, we do.
你叫  普林斯
It's, um... Prince?
有同名的黑人歌手
狗屎运猜中的
Lucky guess.
我刚刚在烤肉台那边
I was over at the carving station,
我就想"你知道谁会想吃牛肋排吗
and I thought, "You know who'd love some prime rib?
普林斯·布朗校长"
Principal Prince Brown."
玛乔丽  恐怕你我只是
Marjorie, I'm afraid you and I are pawns
这两个人精心策划的变态计划中的两颗棋子
in a very sick game being orchestrated by these two.
她们两个非常努力地想把咱俩撮合到一起
They're working very hard to put us together,
我也不知道为什么
and I don't know why.
我从没见过她们俩努力做任何事
I've never seen them work very hard in anything,
除了逃避志愿工作的时候
except getting out of volunteering.
凭良心讲  我们也志愿做了很多事
Hey, to be fair, we volunteer for plenty of things.
你忘了我提着水管在慈善洗车募款洗车吗
Yeah, don't you remember me holding a hose at the car wash?
精彩画面  永生难忘
Yeah, everybody remembers that.
所以你对我没兴趣是吗
So you're not interested in me?
我们一直以来都是同事间的情谊
Well, we've always had a working relationship,
我可能只是从没想过跟你有那种感情吧
and I guess I've just never thought of you in that way.
男女之情吗
As a woman?
我在工作时会把男女感情抛到九云霄外
When I'm at work, I turn off that part of myself.
现在那感情又上身了
Uh, it has turned back on.
我去检查消防安全门是否畅通
Oh, I'm gonna check the -- the fire exits.
我们去开始把椅子叠起来
We're going to stack chairs.
慢走不送
Whatever.
我想到了
I've got it.
我们创立一个假军乐队
We start a fake marching band
然后先拿一笔购置乐器的款项
and get the money for the instruments up front.
这根本就是电影《欢乐音乐妙无穷》的翻版
You just described the exact plot of "The Music Man."
下场如何
How'd that turn out?
赢了四座托尼奖
Won four Tonys.
是五座
Five. Ugh.
你怎么可以让这种事发生呢
How could you let this happen?
我哪知道啊  你短信我的时候
I don't know. You were texting me
我正好在直播我的早餐...
while I was live streaming my breakfast, and...
等等
Wait a minute.
我说了是八百块啊
I did say $800.
你看
Look.
天啊  那这事真的是我的锅
Oh, my God, this is all my fault.
哎哟哟
Well, well, well.
风水轮流转  傻逼轮流当
Looks like the dunce cap is on the other foot.
艹
Hey!
你这体型的牲畜吃的就是草
Is what an animal your size grazes on.
艹就是草
Hay is...
而你是只大笨牛
You're a cow.
好啦
Okay.
你这块头  你的体重绝对很完美
You're the perfect weight for your frame.
同志内心挣扎的又一经典呈现
Another proud moment for the struggle.
她来啦
Ugh. Here she comes.
斗士玛丁·璐德·妗女士
Martin Luther Queen, yes.
请您务必跟我说说基佬的内心挣扎
By all means, tell me about the struggle.
可以啊  你个毒舌小娘炮
Okay, you nasty little twink.
你对不起我
You owe everything to me
与所有在你之前的男同前辈
and all the gays that came before you.
我们辛苦争取来的一切
It's because of everything we fought for
才让你能不可一世的在高中里混
that you get to snark your way through high school
穿着内增高招摇过市
with lifts in your shoes
而不是被人塞进置物柜里眼泪汪汪
instead of spending it terrified, shoved in a locker.
我十分自豪说出这番话
I was really proud of that.
我坦白告诉你
Just so you know.
洗澡前先用干的刷子去角质
Exfoliating with a dry brush pre-shower
就能够大大得到改善哦
will really help you with all of this.
能让你回到50岁时的年轻状态
It'll make you look 50 again.
接下来的举动我就不是很自豪了
I'm not really proud of what came next.
你连塞人都像个娘们儿
You shove like a girl!
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
到了买单的时候了
The piper needs to be paid.
你还有单没买吗
You hired a piper?
不  是为错误买单  我得扛起责任
No. I made a mistake, and I need to accept the consequences.
各位同学  打扰一下
Classmates, could I have everyone's attention, please?
我有个不太好的消息
I have some troubling news.
我知道你们都觉得我是校园金童
I know you may all think of me as the golden boy,
天才选手  神一般的人物
the prodigy, the wunderkind.
你谁啊
Who are you?
没错
Indeed.
我都要不知道自己是谁了
I'm not sure I know anymore.
我们有个小问题
We have a little situation,
我想尽早跟大家坦白这事
and I just want to be as up front as I can.
等等
Hold on a minute.
我才是主席
I'm the President.
这事该由我来
I should do this.
我们要为一位有困难的同学募款八千元
We need to raise $8,000 for a classmate in need.
如果筹不到这笔钱  他可能得一生瘫痪
If we don't get this money, he may never walk again.
我们会发起一个众筹  如果你想要展现
We're gonna make a Kickstarter, and if you want to show
自己是一位有爱心有善心的人给对象看
your date you're the kind of sensitive, caring person
以获得该有的肉体上奖励
who deserves to be rewarded in a physical way,
你就会慷慨乐捐
you'll give generously.
你真是个大说谎家
Wow, you're a good liar.
我收回我以前的话  当主席你实至名归
I take it back. You deserve to be President.
我们就不应该帮忙把那个小贱人
We never should've helped that little punk
从置物柜里救出来
get out of that locker.
我不知道他会对你的毛衣这么狠啊
I didn't know he was gonna be so brutal about your sweater.
-好了  交出来  -什么
- All right, hand it over. - What?
这里是禁大麻区  你个"麻"烦精
This is a blaze-free zone, wastoid.
这里到处都有我的眼线
I got eyes all over this place.
我知道什么是大麻烟斗
I know what vape is.
-教练  那是我的...  -你的啥
- Coach, that's just my -- - Just your --
教练  能跟你说句话吗
Hey, Coach, can I talk to you for a second?
什么事
Yeah, what's up?
我只是想告诉你
Yeah, I, uh, just wanted to let you know
那个呢...  是他的气喘药吸入器
that that's, uh -- that's his inhaler.
是他的...
It's his -- oh.
你是有什么毛病啊
What is wrong with you?
抱歉了
Sorry.
只是觉得我对他们掏心掏肺
It's just I give everything to these boys,
他们却只觉得我是软柿子
and all they think of me is that I'm a pushover
连整我都懒得整
not even worthy of a lousy prank.
小卡  你有看到歌洛莉亚吗
Cam, have you seen Gloria?
有啊  我上次看到她
What? Yeah, oh, last time I saw her,
她好像是在那一带
she was somewhere over here.
那本来是要倒我头上的
Oh, that was for me!
本来是要来整我的  我的孩子们爱我
That was supposed to be for me! My boys love me!
我就想安静读本书而已
I just wanted to read my book.
你好  我是卢克·邓菲
Oh, hi there. I'm Luke Dunphy,
-学生会主席  -而我...
- Student Body President. - And I'm --
但主角并不是我们
But this isn't about us.
是我们一位碰到难关的同学
We have a classmate who's in a pretty bad spot.
但他的人生不见得得止步于此
But it doesn't have to end that way.
有了您的帮助  我们能让他免于挨打
With your help, we can save him from getting beaten up.
挨病痛的打击
By -- by his disease.
一种任何孩子都不该与之"搏斗"的疾病
A disease no kid should have to wrestle with.
我们只需要筹到八千块
We just need to raise $8,000 to --
或九千块的善款  来让他享受豪华治疗
Or $9,000 to get him that super deluxe treatment.
我们只需要八千块
We only need $8000
我是卢克·邓菲
I'm Luke Dunphy
我大力支持  并为此活动代言
And I am approved this message